foreign
[Music]
would you be interested with it
and I'll let you know
see ya
thank you
[Music]
so welcome back
I'm gonna share with you young I think
Sun safer life
it is the affordable life insurance with
the High coverage so I'm gonna explain
to your new benefits and products
so it has a life insurance coverage with
a minimal cost it has a loan protection
of coverage it's a it has a hassle-free
conversion and it has a flexible payment
mode
insurance coverage at a minimal cost so
this is a peso denominated offering life
insurance protection equivalent to 200
of the fees amount so meaning
that benefit
when it comes to the face amount this is
also a five-year renewable convertible
term every five years the increase young
premium individuals
so um also it has a long period of
Protection cover until age 75. so
good luck
age 75.
until age 75. it automatically renews
every after five years
it has a hassle-free conversion meaning
you can convert this product into either
a whole life our endowment or a visual
product right before you age 65. options
to get a product
investment dividends
in the future however it cannot be
converted to Saint Pete and Wilson
Cancer Care inside ICU protect because
these products are living benefits so
foreign
mode so you can choose either annual
semi-annual or quarterly you also have
the option to have it monthly throughout
the debit or Auto charging so please
take note since this is a traditional
product model Factor once you choose to
pay semi-annual or quarterly increase
but it's still an additional premium for
you
however since this is a very affordable
plan this has no savings components
for your life insurance coverage benefit
coverage
among Riders available for life are
accidental death benefit and total
disability benefit so accidental death
benefit this is an additional Indemnity
given to the beneficiary remember it is
given to the beneficiary if in case the
cause of your debt as insured is
accident apart don't set guaranteed that
benefit like biblical benefit
additional Indemnity
because of accident
we also have the total disability
benefit which is a waiver of premium
upon Insurance diagnosis of total
disability whether temporary or
permanent so it means total disability
um you are not capable of doing your
usual jobs
so in that case because you have this
River premium
company
I totally disabled you need to submit um
documents coming from The Physician
certifying that you are still totally
disabled however
capacity of course
premium payment okay this is a sample
illustration just to let you know for
this um illustration we have the face
amount of 1 billion remember the debt
benefit of this product is 200 of the
face amount so automatic 2 million young
if we begin the death benefits
a month so again every five years
premium if you can see from age 30 and
premium is 12 300 per year it comes age
35 lagging 12 560 per year
260 pesos
until age 75. foreign
amount
780 compared to 56 940 lemon
and you want to increase on your life
coverage you might want to think about
this sun safer life then financial
advisor
just to give you a preference
smoker
issue ages
1 million phase a month a minimum phase
for life is one million so meaning a
minimum death benefit is 2 million pesos
you can screenshot this parame reference
camp and please take note long that this
is a smoker
um
so why should you get this
million pesos
it can be a good start with flexibility
to convert in another type of policy
um
then you can convert it into the plan
that you want
so you just have to undergo conversion
and program
it can have the option to continue or
not
just pay the premium if you don't want
to continue your coverage you can stop
paying the premium you can compare this
product into HMO car insurance
you continue your HMO congus
you continue with the car insurance
then you continue paying your premium
with sun safer life now if this product
is good for you and you want to discuss
further about this just check the
description below and I'll let you know
what to do
so
again catch me guys in Facebook
Instagram as your vice president if
you're um interested with this kind of
video just click the like button and
subscribe
upcoming videos
and some other financial management tips
and also we have the TP travel tips
already so see you all
thank you